http://www.frc.org/privacy-policy

Featured
Founded in 1983, Family Research Council is a nonprofit research and educational organization dedicated to articulating and advancing a family-centered philosophy of public life. In addition to providing policy research and analysis for the legislative, executive, and judicial branches of the federal government, FRC seeks to inform the news media, the academic community, business leaders, and the general public about family issues that affect the nation from a biblical worldview.
About FRC
Vision & Mission
History
FRC Staff
State Groups
FAQs
Directions
Employment
Recent Publications
Taxpayer Funding of Abortion and Abortion BusinessesReligious Freedom in China: The History, Current Challenges, and the Proper Response to a Human Rights CrisisNo Proof of Harm
Washington Watch
Broadcast Archives
Radio Stations
Email the Show
Recent Broadcasts
Mike Pompeo, Mark Hotaling, Shaan Taseer, Tony PerkinsMike Johnson, Lela Gilbert, Mike McClure, David Closson
News
Press Releases
Op-Eds
Washington Update
Blog
COVID-19 and the Church Resources
Recent Activity
FRC Welcomes State Dept.'s Addition of Nigeria to List of World's Worst Religious Freedom ViolatorsFamily Research Council Defends the Hyde Amendment as House Democrats Try to Eliminate It
Events
Speaker Series
Upcoming Events
Previous Events
Pastor Events
Recent Activity
Pray Vote Stand - December 9Pray Vote Stand - December 2
Keyword Search
Privacy Policy
FRC 's commitment to your privacy. We believe the relationships we have with our supporters are key to our continued success. Therefore, it is important for us to provide you with a clear understanding of how we utilize your personal information. How we store your personal information. When you provide us with your name and contact information, it is recorded in a secure database that is owned and managed by FRC. How we use your personal information. FRC values your privacy, and never sells or rents constituent information to third parties.  On rare occasion, FRC may decide to exchange lists containing e-mail and/or postal address information of our constituency with like-minded organizations whose missions closely resemble that of Family Research Council, such as our sister organization, FRC Action.  Upon request via postal mail, e-mail, or telephone, Family Research Council will provide to those which inquire, a summary of any personally identifiable information retained by FRC regarding their direct information and the identity of other organizations who have been provided their personal information within the past 12 month period. FRC constituents may modify, correct, change or update their own personally identifiable information that FRC has collected or opt out of communication from us at any time by contacting Family Research Council online, via postal mail or by telephone at 1-800-225-4008 during regular business hours.
How we track visitors to the web site. An IP address is the unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you log onto the Internet. As you enter FRC 's site, our server records and monitors your IP address and uses it to develop aggregated statistical analysis. These analyses assist us in refining and adapting the content and design of our site. The use of IP addresses also enables us to prevent malicious Internet users from masquerading as other users. How we use "Cookies." A cookie is a piece of text or data that can be stored in the memory of your web browser. This data can only be retrieved by the server/domain that places the cookie. FRC employs cookies for the following purposes: -- To hold shopping cart data (items that you wish to purchase). -- To enable automatic form validation/entry (if "remember me" is selected in site store). -- To enable online polling (cookies allow us to limit a user's response to one). -- To compile statistics concerning items offered online. FRC NEVER stores financial or Credit Card data within cookies. Those who feel uncomfortable with cookie technology can disable cookies within their browser settings. FRC .org is designed to operate with or without cookies. However, some functionality will be removed when cookies are disabled. Disabling cookies will prevent participation in online polling and could result in the loss of shopping cart information. The option to cancel mailings and emails. Upon registering, you may begin receiving communications from us. These messages will always contain unsubscribe instructions. If you would like to correct, update, add, or delete personal information, simply let us know by clicking here or telephoning 1-800-225-4008 Mondays through Fridays 8:30 AM to 5:30 PM . Surveys. From time to time our site may request information from users via surveys. Participation is completely voluntary. Information requested may include demographic information (such as age and zip code). This information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Recording information from "email this page to a friend." If a user elects to use our referral service to inform a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's email address for the purpose of sending the requested information. The recipient may receive a few emails of interest, and their information will be purged in 60 days if they do not opt-in to further communications FRC.Acceptance of Privacy Policy. By using this site and services, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Policy, your only remedy is to discontinue use of this site and services. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we change our policy, we will post those changes on our site so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Your continued use of any portion of the site following the posting of such changes will constitute your acceptance of those changes. Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you. You should always exercise caution whenever disclosing information online.
Issues
Life and Human Dignity
Religious Liberty and Conscience
Marriage, Family and Sexuality
Civil Society
Washington Watch
Broadcast Archives
Radio Stations
